Munim Dibosh

Product Designer

Dhaka, Bangladesh <u>abdulmunim.buet@gmail.com</u> | <u>http://dibosh.me/</u> +880 - 1946923667

I have been involved with designing usable interfaces for more than 2 years and been into software development nearly for 5 years now. Having clear understanding of product and user experience design, enabled me to become one of the key design decision makers in every company I have worked for. Looking forward to working with a team of passionate people who share the same dream and work relentlessly to solve a problem that makes millions of lives easier.

SKILLS

Interface Design - Logo/Brand/Identity Design - Interaction Design - UX Design - Frontend Development - Software Engineering - Scrum Master/Product Management

EXPERIENCE

NewsCred Inc, Dhaka Office - Full Stack Engineer (Full Time)

AUGUST 2014 - PRESENT

NewsCred is one of the leading content marketing solution providers. They provide Content Marketing software as a service.

- Initially joined as Product Designer for one of the core teams and provided UX solutions along with front end development in AngularJS for more than 1 year
- Was part of developing an interactive interface for original content clients to solicit ideas from their freelancers on top of MEAN stack
- Improved and developed a whole new story writing experience inside Content Marketing Cloud application; mostly vanilla JS
- Designed and developed a reporting dashboard used by sales team on top of AngularJS

Lantas Tech, Dhaka - UX Engineer & Product Owner (Part Time Consultant)

APRIL 2015 - PRESENT

Lantas Tech is a small startup with a revolutionary idea of developing a micro CRM for enterprises.

- Researched and developed the whole product roadmap from scratch
- Designed the whole experience of the micro CRM mobile application and owned the design team of 2 person to do branding and all

 Introduced Scrum and as a Product Owner directed the product outcome and milestones

ManGoesMobile, Dhaka - Software Engineer (20 hours/week)

NOVEMBER 2011 - JULY 2014

ManGoesMobile was a small startup founded by an ex-Googler focused to work on third world problems and building tools for them.

- Developed a telemedicine system for doctors all over the world in both iOS and Android
- Designed and developed an interactive form creation and submission process for a group messaging application, in Android, using OpenDataKit

EDUCATION

Bangladesh University of Engineering & Technology, Dhaka

B.Sc in Computer Science & Engineering 2009 - 2014

Thesis - A mobile approach to find nearby bus stoppages in Dhaka, with optimal hop number to reach destination from a predefined source.

TOOLS & OTHERS

Project Management- Scrum Framework, Jira

Design- Sketch, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, HTML, CSS, SASS

Programming Languages- C, Java, Javascript, Python, ObjectiveC

Frameworks- Node.JS, Angular.JS

AWARDS & CERTIFICATES

Certified Scrum Master

This is a certification from Scrum Alliance™ after a certain training program on Scrum and Agile methodologies. Certified persons are qualified to direct a Scrum team.

Microsoft Imagine Cup, National Round, 4th Position

Microsoft Imagine Cup is considered to be the Olympic of Software Engineering contests. The certification is for securing 4th position among 114 teams in total.

DESIGN PORTFOLIO (.pdf)

Download- https://goo.gl/eSmKpT